塞勒姆前情回顾
Previously on "Salem"...
女巫
Witch!
在塞勒姆还从没有女人有那种权力
No woman in Salem has ever had that kind of power.
即使是玛丽 西布利也没有
Not even Mary Sibley.
那屋子的女主人是我的
The lady of the house is mine.
我们已经发现了一个巫师
We've uncovered a witch.
这回您会在镇上呆多久
How long may we enjoy your curative presence in town?
一直到塞勒姆镇最后一个卖身魔鬼的女巫死光
Until every last Devil's whore of a witch in Salem is dead.
柏翠的巫术只能维持一天
Petrus' physic will last but a day,
然后 西布利会醒来 神志清楚
and then Mr. Sibley will awake, lucid and eager.
会亟不可待地告诉因科瑞斯一切
To tell Increase everything.
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
翻译：慕斯 柯小南 呆毛 elsa 肉丝 vera强妹
校对：柯小南
选一个
Choose one.
喝吧
Drink.
后期：hhjie
享受的喝下去
Drink and... Enjoy.
只有凡人易受俗物的诱惑
Only mere mortals are vulnerable to man-made spirits.
作为人类来说 你真的很令人憎恶
As a man, you are an abomination,
时间轴：阿黎
但你还不是巫师
but you are no witch.
现在你可以和你那个令人可怜的软弱 一起滚开了
Now begone with you and your... Pitiful weakness.
总监：柯小南
该起床了 我的好夫人
Time to wake, my good madam.
让他们不能再说 上帝会安排一切
Let them no more say, "God must do all,"
以此来教唆他们
and so encourage themselves
从此远离上帝 也远离内心的
to live in a careless neglect of God and of their own souls
救赎
and salvation!
魔鬼已经把这个村庄搞得不成样子
The Devil has made a dreadful knot of witches in the country,
并且在巫师的帮助下
and, by the help of witches,
变本加厉的继续破坏
has dreadfully Increased that knot.
孩子们啊 提高一些警惕吧
Oh, children, children, be afraid
睡觉前一定要祈祷
and go not prayerless to your bed
这样才不会做噩梦
lest the Devil be your bedfellow.
早上好  牧师
Good morning, Reverend.
啊
Ah.
西布里夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
要一起吗
Join me.
您对
There are no words
我丈夫的再造之恩
to encompass my overwhelming gratitude
我的感激难以言表
at your reclamation of my husband.
如果不是您在
When I think what might have transpired
-后果真的难以想象 -是么
had you not been there  -Indeed?
那究竟会有什么后果呢
Exactly what might have transpired?
-什么  -我的意思是
Excuse me? -  Well...
你家的女仆难道不会直接送他去医院吗
Would not your slave girl simply have taken him on to hospital?
当然可以
Yes.
没错 不就是你派她去救他嘛
Yes, it was you who sent her to his rescue,
不是吗
was it not?
我一听说立马就派她去了
Once I'd heard of the accident.
啊
Ah.
不过 我还是很困惑
I am perplexed, though.
告诉我 你为什么这么着急想要把乔治秘密带出去
Tell me, why was George scurried off with such haste and secrecy?
他经常去波士顿
He goes often to Boston.
-去看病  -他没生病
- His illness... - He's not ill.
-他是被下蛊了 -他没有
He's spelled. Mary: No.
那不可能
That's impossible.
好好想想
Consider...
乔治是不是无缘无故的病了好多年
has not George suffered this mysterious malady
病了好多年
without explication for several years now,
而且没有一个医生能说出病因
and have not the doctors expressed utter befuddlement
说出病因
as to its cause?
-没错 但是 -是吧
Yes, but... - Yes.
这样说来
In such cases,
答案就显而易见了
the answer is oft the simplest one.
乔治没有生病
George is not ill.
他是被邪恶的魔鬼控制了
He is under the influence of the Devil's darkest tool...
是巫师的咒语
a witch's spell.
而且下周的人似乎与她非常亲近
And it is quite likely that this speller resides close at hearth.
不可能
No.
也许就在你家的某个地方
Perhaps even in the hallowed halls of your own home.
说吧
Say it.
说什么
Say what?
控告
The accusation.
你一定忍了很久了
It dances on your tongue.
好吧 我确信你误会我了
Well, I assure you, you are mistaken.
呃
Hm.
现在我想立刻把我的丈夫接回家
Then I wish to bring my husband home immediately.
你不能这样做 西布利夫人
I think not, Mrs. Sibley.
你有什么权利拒绝我
You would deny me that right?
在找到施咒者之前
I must deny you that right
我不得不拒绝你
until we can discover the origin of the spell.
嗯
Hmm?
那我坚持
Then I would ask, or, rather, insist,
需要有人照顾西布利先生
that someone attend to Mr. Sibley.
最好是有这种经验的人
Someone who has experience with his travails.
那个年轻人怎么样
What about that young man...
就是那个在他去波士顿的人
the one who was to take him to Boston, huh?
-以撒么 -没错
Isaac? -  Ah.
可以
Isaac will do.
他还在昏迷吗
He sleeps still?
有侍卫在看守他
Under the care of sentries.
对了  玛丽
Oh, and, Mary.
你大可放心
Be of good heart.
酒吧老板兰姆先生说他可能随时醒来
Mr. Lamb, the barkeep, tells me that he may wake at any moment.
柯顿
Cotton.
除了心还在跳以外
No difference between me and those that already rest.
我和那些死人没什么区别
Besides a still-beating heart
现在我只是一个有灵魂的空壳罢了
in a shell where my soul no longer resides.
天呐
Oh, boy.
早上好 牧师
Good morning, Reverend.
我在想
I Wonder...
你要怎样才能重新站起来
what would it take to get you to your feet?
你为什么这样想
Why would you wish to?
我害怕我可能
I fear I may have...
以前对你的评判太毫不留情了 麦哲教士
Judged you too harshly, Reverend Mather.
直到现在 当我已经远离童年的时候
It is only now, when leaving my childhood behind,
我才意识到 我们无论是现在还是将来
that I realize we are, past and forever,
都是父亲的孩子
our fathers' children.
我们不能控制他们是谁
And we can no more control who they be
和他们是怎样影响我们的
and how they came to form us
如果那样的话我们都能操纵太阳的东升西落了
then we can the rise and setting of the sun.
对于你爱的女孩我感到很抱歉
I am sorry about your girl.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们能送你回家吗
May we see you home?
起来吧
Come on.
等他安定下来了 上尉
Once he's settled, captain,
我能请你帮个忙吗
may I ask a favor of you?
当然
Surely.
我不这么认为 西布利女士
"I think not, Mrs. Sibley."
说得好像他是苏格拉底 而我只是他膝下学生一样
As if he were socrates and I, a student at his knee.
让我杀了他吧 可以吗
Let me kill him, please.
不可以
No.
让我为你减轻这个负担吧
Let me ease this burden for you,
-就像我对其他事情那样 -玛丽：英克瑞斯 麦哲
- as I've done the others. - Mary: Increase Mather is known
是全世界家喻户晓的人物 老少皆知
throughout the world, new and old.
他的失踪或死亡不能轻描淡写的对待
His disappearance or death will not be taken lightly.
他的项上人头不能放在任何一个人的木盘里
His head will sit on no man's platter.
他可比不上你 这是一定的
He's no match for you, certainly.
这就是你做错的地方 孩子
That is where you are wrong, child.
真正的考验就是让我们与势均力敌的人战斗
This is our truest test To battle equals.
西布利女士
Rev. Lewis: Mrs. Sibley.
牧师
Reverend.
黙茜
Mercy.
你好
Hello.
我想知道 我可以
Rev. Lewis: I wonder if I might have a private word
和我的女儿私下里说几句吗
with my daughter.
我觉得不行 牧师
I think not, Reverend.
我 -玛丽：把艾萨克带来
I... -Mary: Fetch me Isaac.
现在
Now.
我是 呃
Rev. Lewis: I am, um...
为你对我女儿的仁慈感到惊讶
Astounded at the charity you've shown my child,
但如果我想要见她 这难道不是一个父亲的权利吗
but if I wish to see her, is that not a father's right?
你为什么 偏偏想要见她 牧师
Why, in particular, do you wish to see her, Reverend?
你还在考虑另一个驱魔仪式吗
Were you perhaps considering another exorcism?
你的日子难道会日渐无趣
Do your days grow dull,
缺少了这个孩子给你鞭打虐待
lacking a child to beat and torture
少了一个可以拜访的女儿 夜晚也会变得孤独吗
and the nights far too lonely with no daughter to visit?
-路易斯牧师：我永远不会 -玛丽：默茜是我的人
- Rev. Lewis: I would never... - Mary: Mercy is mine.
你再到这里一次 我就会公开指控你的这些罪行
Return here again and these accusations will be made public.
西布利大人怎么样了 他醒了吗
What of master Sibley? Has he woken?
长老会的人不能再等了
The elders will wait no longer.
他们需要你带着观众去
They require an audience with you today.
他醒了吗
Has he woken?
任何时候都行
Any moment now.
这只是个意外 女士
It were an accident, ma'am.
在路上有一个绊脚的木材
A wayward timber in the path,
结果我们六七点钟才醒过来
and we found ourselves at sixes and sevens.
没关系 艾萨克
It's okay, Isaac.
我知道你已经尽力了
I know you've done your best.
牧师在叫我了
The Reverend summons me now,
天知道是为什么 但我害怕再让他多等一秒
heaven knows why, but I fear each second he's made to wait...
他会让你看着西不里先生
He will ask you to watch over Mr. Sibley.
他会吗 -玛丽：在我的坚持下
He will? - Mary: At my grave insistence,
既然他已经拒绝了我的愿望
since he refuses my desire
不让我把我的丈夫带回家好好照顾
to bring my husband home to proper care.
他拒绝了你
He refuses you?
塞勒姆镇像是一个笨拙的陀螺一样
Salem reels out of control like an unwieldy spin top
在英克瑞斯 麦哲的小聪明的带领下
at the whim of Increase Mather.
一种药 施加睡眠的痛苦与放松
A tonic... the pain and ease of sleep.
艾萨克 我求求你
Isaac, I beseech you,
在这件秘密而又重要的事情上
in this most private and important matter,
完成我做不到的恳求
do my bidding where I cannot.
哦 呃
Oh, uh...
立刻给他下药并且让他一直沉睡下去
Dose him immediately and keep him so.
乔治不应该被强迫着承受
George should not be made to suffer
老麦哲毫无根据的怀疑
for Mather senior's unfounded suspicions.
他 他不应该
H-he shall not.
艾萨克
And Isaac...
记得保密
Between us.
就像是塞勒姆镇的许多秘密一样
Like so many of Salem's secrets.
保密
Between us.
-英克瑞斯：你知道吗 孩子
- Increase: Are you aware, son?
你的故事在这块土地上已经传了很远 臭名昭著
Your story is known far and wide throughout the land.
私通者艾萨克
Isaac the fornicator.
不 不 不 不要羞耻的低下你的头
No, no, no. Do not bow your head in shame.
抬头 昂起你的头颅
Head up. Get your head up.
抬头 抬头
Head up. Head up.
私通者艾萨克的故事
The story of Isaac the fornicator
是神圣的
is a holy one.
我们清教徒把它当做一个活着的先例
It is used as a living precedent by we puritans
来向我们的孩子讲述诱惑的邪恶
to illustrate to the children the evils of lust.
不 不 你的罪与罚
No, no. Your sin and your suffering...
被转化成了伟大而又神圣的祝福
it has been transformed into a great and a holy blessing.
因为 我的孩子
For, my son...
你感受到了上帝之手
You felt the hand of God.
他触摸了你
He's touched you.
他在改变你
He's working through you.
他选中了你
He's chosen you.
不
No.
有多少人能说自己是被上帝选中的
How many can say that they have been chosen by God?
被选中来做什么
Chosen for what?
孩子 你有没有想过除了塞勒姆之外的地方
Son, have you ever imagined a world beyond Salem?
-嗯 -我
- Hmm? -I...
抬起头来 抬起你的头
Get your head up, your head up,
抬起来 抬起来
your head up, your head up.
先生 我在这活得很好
I have a good life here, sir.
为西布利夫人做些琐碎的杂事
Yes, performing meager errands for Mrs. Sibley.
她对我一直很好
She's been good to me. Always.
她的慈善让你站在她的那一方
Her charity binds you to her bidding.
不不不不 以撒
No. No, no, no, Isaac.
在这之外
Out there.
孩子 在这以外
Out there, boy!
世界这么大
There's a vast world out there,
机遇这么多
full of... full of opportunities,
只要你抬起头
and if you... if you would walk the straight road
沿着这街走下去
in the sunlight with your head up,
我会带着你去看的
I would take you with me to see it.
我会的
I would.
你想要吗
Would you like that?
我要做什么
What would I have to do?
嗯
Well...
你要做的是
You will have to...
站在西布利先生这一边
have to tend to Mr. Sibley there.
你要做的是
You'll have to...
确保他的安全和健康
Make certain that he is fresh and tidy,
你要知道 这并不容易
and that is no easy task, hmm?
最重要的是 他一醒来你就要告知于我
Most importantly, you must alert me the moment that he wakes.
嗯
Yes.
你可以么
Can you do that, hmm?
我能问一下么 先生
Do you mind me asking, sir,
这些是干嘛的
what these are for?
帮助西布利先生抵抗
Protection for Mr. Sibley against...
外界的阻力的
Outer forces.
这些都是一个
It's cremated ash...
200岁女巫的骨灰
Of a 200-year-old witch.
还有 以撒
And, Isaac...
我亲手烧了她
I burned her myself.
房顶 这里和这里 要修补
So, the roof needs patching there and there,
新涂的这层油漆不会坏
a fresh coat of paint wouldn't hurt,
还需要四到五个床给这些小一点的孩子
nor would four or five more beds for the smaller children,
我吓到你了
and... I'm overwhelming you.
没 没
No, no.
我渴望将我的精力都付出
I'm eager to put my energies to good.
是的
Exactly.
船长 这些孩子都吓到了
The children are frightened, Captain.
被今天的这个悬尸还有未知的死亡吓到了
Another hung today and not an inkling who's to be next.
他们都不知道哪一个更令人害怕了
They're unsure who to fear more...
女巫还是追捕他们的人
witches or those who pursue them.
那 谁能指责他们呢
Well, who can blame them?
他不和别人一起玩
He doesn't play with the others.
那个深色头发的男孩
The dark-haired boy.
他在这已经两年了
He's been here two years.
他的父母被印度人杀了
His parents were murdered by Indians.
他们说他全看见了
They say he saw.
没有人知道他怎么活下来的
No one knows how he survived.
有人问过么
Has anyone asked?
他从不说
He doesn't talk.
至少 自从那时起
At least, not anymore.
就再也不说话了
Not since... Then.
你好
Excuse me.
你知道如何补屋顶么
Do you know anything about patching a roof?
西布利夫人
Mrs. Sibley?
她不在
The mistress is out.
哦
Oh.
你要和她说的也可以和我说说
Anything needed to be said to her can be said to me.
噢  真可爱
Oh, that's beautiful!
我的仆人
My familiar.
仆人
Familiar?
魔鬼赠与的礼物用来执行我的命令的
A gift from the Devil to do my bidding,
我的精神伴侣
my spiritual companion.
这就是她怎么吃东西的
This is how she feeds.
我会有一个仆人么
Will I get a familiar?
假以时日
In time.
我该如何选择
How do I choose?
你不要选的
You don't.
它选择你
It chooses you.
西布利夫人 你好啊
Good day, Mrs. Sibley.
孩子们
Girls.
我们去墓地见默茜
We're off to meet Mercy in the graveyard.
好的
Well.
那去吧
On your way, then.
我们对她的损失都很遗憾
We all grieve the loss of our sister.
我承认
I do not argue this.
但要记住 我没得选择
But beg remembrance that I was given little choice.
潘多拉之盒
The malum...
是这个仪式不可或缺的
Without which our grand rite would not be possible.
露丝把它带到这 要使用这死亡的工具
Rose brought it here, this instrument of death,
没有我的学识 来挑战我打败我
without my knowledge, to challenge and defeat me.
这是给你们的 为我们的事业承受报复的代价
It is for you, retrieved at great cost,
放弃爱和热情
relinquished with love and ardor for our cause.
我只给你们留下这世间
I leave you now with the only tool
唯一可以控制我的
that exists on earth to control me.
诀窍就是劈开它们
The trick to making shakes is to split them...
不是砍 不是锯 而是劈
not chopped or sawed, but to split.
谢谢
Thank you.
换你了
Your turn.
对 就这样
Right! Well done.
上尉
Captain.
西布利夫人
Mrs. Sibley.
小伙子
Young man.
你去看看那边有没有清水
Why don't you go see if there's any fresh water.
什么风把你刮来啦
Big doings this morning.
惊喜天天见 没什么稀罕的
Seems every day brings its fair share of surprises.
听说老英克瑞斯抓了你丈夫
I heard old Increase took possession of your husband.
是的
Yes, he did.
我很想把他救回来
And I'm eager to get him back.
真假的
You are?
怎么了
Why?
这很奇怪么 上尉先生
Is it so unusual, Captain,
一个妻子想要丈夫回家这很正常啊
for a wife to want her husband at home?
大多数情况下的确很正常
In most cases, it's not unusual at all.
听说我辛苦干活的老公口渴啦
I heard my hard worker was thirsty.
哦 西布利夫人
Oh, Mrs. Sibley.
额 这里有新鲜的苹果汁
Uh, fresh apple water on offer.
不了 谢谢你 安妮
No, thank you, Anne.
再见了 上尉 小伙子
Good day, Captain. Young man.
上尉
Captain.
我可以吗
May I?
-先生好  -你好
Sir. - Man: Good morrow.
你要是想要对你的弱点屈服
If you're going to capitulate to your weakness,
非要这样公之于众吗
must it be on constant public display?
那让你来公之于众怎么样
Shall I leave public display to you, father?
我们应当废了绞刑
Shall we abolish the noose
好让你用自己的双手拧断自己的脖子
so that you may break necks with your own two hands?
她之前就死了
She was dead.
那个妓女走私者是自杀的
The whore runner killed herself.
她既然已经死了
She was already dead,
你还把她上绞刑吗
and yet you hung her.
我说了她会被绞死
I said she would hang.
她就得给我绞死
And hang she did.
人无信 无以立
We are nothing if we do not keep our word,
恐怕你还不明白这个道理吧
a principle which seems to mean very little to you, I fear.
你真的要这么恨我吗
Must you hate me so?
哦 柯顿
Oh, Cotton.
你母亲也叫柯顿 这你是知道的
Your mother was a Cotton, as you know.
她是我的异父的妹妹
And my stepsister.
我们的婚姻是历史必然的结果
Our marriage was a historical inevitability.
柯顿家族和麦哲家族
The cottons and the Mathers...
谁能抵挡的了
who could resist such a...
如此权力和声望的结合
such a joining of... of power and prestige?
你肯定不能
Certainly not you.
她是个好女人
She was a good woman,
是个合格的母亲
and she was a fit enough mother,
不过
but...
我并不爱她
I didn't love her.
我不知道爱为何物
I didn't love.
于是 你诞生了
And then you were born.
成了现在这个
And there you were, a...
哭哭啼啼的一团废物
Squalling mess of limbs and of hair, and...
你成不了大器
You weren't much.
不过你让我知道了爱
But you were enough to show me love.
这可真特么讽刺啊
What utter irony
你将从我这里遗传到同样的东西
that you would then take the self-same thing from me.
啊
Henry: Ah!
先生 你没钱了 我们不卖给你了
You are cut off, sir!
不 我有钱
No. I have money!
我还可以喝喝喝
I will drink muchly and often!
你不会 给我滚
You will not. Now be on your way.
-谁说的 -哦 不不 滚
I think not. - Lamb: Oh, no, no. Whoa. Go!
美酒来自上帝
The wine is from God.
酒鬼来自地狱
The drunkard is from the Devil.
振作起来
Pull yourself together.
路还远着呢
There's much work to be done.
让我杀了他
Let me kill him.
我告诉过你
I have told you.
我们不能杀英克瑞斯
We cannot kill Increase.
我说的不是又老又蠢的老英克瑞斯
Not silly old Increase.
西布利夫人
Mr. Sibley.
你就是这样教她的么
This is what you teach her?
遇到问题第一个想的办法居然是谋杀
For any problem, murder is the first course of action?
我们不能杀乔治
We cannot kill George.
为何不
Why not?
您一个人的力量就已经非常强大了
You are so powerful You alone.
你不需要他
- You do not need him. - Mary:
你错就错在这里 亲爱的
That is where you are wrong, my dear.
我们非常需要他
We need him desperately.
没有了乔治 就等于没有了一切
Without George, it all goes away.
我就成了一个一无所有的寡妇
I am a widow with nothing...
没有生意可做 在市镇委员中也没有发言权
no business to run, no voice with the selectmen.
只要他活着 我就可以通过他说话
With him alive, I can speak through him...
让他成为一个被操控意志和思想的木偶
a puppet to parrot his wishes and thoughts.
但是 一旦他死了他就没用了 而我也将一点权力也没有了
But dead, he is useless and I am without power.
不过你如何让他不说话呢
But how will you stop him from speaking?
我会进入他的头脑 从里面毁灭一切
I will enter his mind and destroy it from within.
他的肉身会活着 不过意志将会死去
His body will live on, but his mind will be gone.
那你怎么能做到呢
How will you do that?
闭嘴吧 你问的太多了
Quiet girl! That is enough questions.
你别想让我安静
Don't you tell me to be quiet.
-闭嘴 -够了
Quiet. - Mary: Enough!
你们两个给我出去
Both of you, leave me now.
-但是我可以帮你啊 -滚
But I can help you. - Mary: Get out!
放开我
Let go of me!
-嘘 -给我放开
Shh! - Mercy: Let go!
你知道我们会杀谁吗
You know who we could kill?
你
You.
你敢 她不会让你得逞的
You can't. She would never let you.
也许会 也许不会
Maybe, maybe not.
你不会想知道的
You don't want to find out.
你这个自私狠毒卑鄙的女人
You're jealous and spiteful and awful.
我等了好多好多年了
Years... I have waited many, many years.
给我滚远远儿的 你个贱人
Stay out of my way, you little bitch.
西布利夫人一直细心照料你
Mrs. Sibley's only ever had your best interest at heart.
不过
Yet still...
在你最绝望的时候
Your moment's worst desperation,
你喊的居然不是她的名字
it was not her name you uttered for rescue
却是老教父麦哲的名字
but that of the Reverend Mather senior.
你说我
What do I,
这么了解你的心狠手辣
who have known only violence and malice from your eager hands,
怎么会在乎你被折磨成什么样子呢
care a whit about your rosy outlook?
玛丽
Mary.
终于拜托了你的控制
Free of your precious familiar,
我终于可以自由的做梦了
I finally got hold of my dreams back.
嗯 对你这如此黑暗扭曲的心灵来说
Hmm. A beatific choice
未尝不是个美好的选择呢
for such a dark and twisted mind.
你记得我们来过这儿吗
You remember coming here?
记得 来这野餐过
Yes. A picnic. - George:
唯独这天我几乎没有鄙视你
The one and only day I almost didn't despise you.
你从来没给过我机会
You never gave me a chance.
你心意已决
Your mind was long made up.
这能怪我吗
Can you blame me?
你偷走了我的人生
You stole my life.
现在你也偷走了我的人生
And now you've stolen mine.
我们离得很近
We are close.
非常近
So very close.
盛大的仪式马上就要完成了
The grand rite is almost complete.
接下来呢
And then what?
去统治另一个国家
Another kingdom for you to rule?
是的
Yes.
一个我不再需要你的国度
A world in which I no longer need you.
一个你终于死去的美好国度
A blessed world in which you can finally die.
这是威胁挑衅的节奏啊
Peril and threats.
四面楚歌  成王败寇
Many a union has relied on less.
不要这么害怕啊 乔治
Don't look so worried, George.
我们还有点路要走
We're a little ways off yet.
现在 我只需要你给我闭上嘴
For now, I just need you quiet,
像天使一般 睡在你肮脏的尿布里
sleeping like an angel in your dirty bibs and nappies.
永别了 乔治
Farewell, George.
你个贱人
You bitch!
贱人
哦 那个混蛋
Oh, that bastard.
-西布利 -英克瑞斯 麦哲
Sibley? - Mary: Increase Mather.
他也在场
He was there.
保护着乔治
Protecting George.
在梦里也在捍卫乔治的灵魂
Guarding his mind even in sleep.
我们还有个问题
We have another problem.
我们必须处理一下那个女孩
We must do something about the girl.
黙茜
Mercy.
她可不可靠
She is... Unreliable.
到我们无法控制她现在
It is only a matter of time before
只是时间问题了
we can no longer control her.
像这个时候
At a time such as this
我比任何时候都有可能被发现
when I am nearer to discovery and annihilation
然后被铲除掉
than ever before,
你却因为嫉妒
you would distract yourself
和那些恶意重伤让自己分心
with petty jealousy and spiteful accusations.
我试着要
I am trying to make...
我现在真的比任何时候都需要你
Never have I needed you more.
但是我却比任何时候都对你感到失望
And never have you disappointed me so gravely.
我愿意为你做一切
I would do anything for you.
我爱你
I love you.
噢 我倒喜欢你不爱我
Oh, and I wish to God you didn't.
爱我少一点 也许会更好
Love me less and you will love me better.
想办法接近乔治
Find a way to get to George.
明天我们将会喷漆
Tomorrow, we'll work on the paint.
当然如果你还有空的话
That is, if you're still available, of course.
漂亮
Excellent.
干得漂亮 孩子
Excellent, son.
斯特凡
Stephen.
你见过我的女儿的
You've seen my daughter.
你可以走了  这里只有孩子
You can move along. There's kids here.
我就是在找一个孩子  我的孩子
I'm looking for a kid... my kid.
而我也说了 快滚吧
And I said, "Move along."
霍普金斯先生
Mr. Hopkins.
有什么可以帮你的吗
How can we help you?
我入狱之后  我女儿是不是待在这里
My daughter came to stay here after when I was in jail?
艾米莉
Emily?
不  霍普金斯先生  她没有
No, Mr. Hopkins. She did not.
你在这儿附近见过她吗
Have you seen her around?
不  先生  我没有
No, sir. I haven't.
噢
Oh.
告诉她我在找她
You tell her I'm looking for her.
告诉她 她得回家了
You tell her she needs to come home.
好的  霍普金斯先生  我会的
Yes, Mr. Hopkins. I'll do that.
利兹
Lizzy...
你把鸡毛和干马粪
Did you bring the chicken feathers
带来了吗
and the dried horse dung?
鸡毛我带来了  但是马粪不太干
I brung the feathers, but the dung weren't dry.
那老鼠呢
And what about the mice?
猫把陷阱里的老鼠都吓跑了
They scattered when the cat come to the trap.
默兮马上就要到了
Mercy is to be here any minute.
什么事都要我亲自做吗
Must I do everything myself?
霍普金斯小姐  能借一步说话吗
Miss Hopkins, may I have a word?
你父亲被释放了
Your father has been freed.
知道了
I see.
他正在找你
And he's been looking for you,
说让你马上回家
asks that you come home immediately.
霍尔小姐
Miss Hale.
有什么可以帮忙的吗
Can we help you?
我只是来告诉霍普金斯小姐
I've only come to tell Miss Hopkins
她父亲被释放了
that her father has been freed.
你人可真好
How kind.
他似乎
And that he seemed...
喝了个大醉什么都不知道了
Quite inebriated and not himself,
也许她今晚最好先别回家
and that perhaps she oughtn't to go home tonight.
或许可以在孤儿院待上一晚 在那儿她会比较安全
Perhaps she ought to stay in the orphanage where she'd be safe.
她跟我们在一起
She is safe.
很安全的
With us.
是吗
Is she?
或许你可以留下
Would you care to stay and...
亲眼见证
See for yourself...
安
Anne?
但不是今晚
Not tonight.
住手
Stop.
那是什么
What is that?
止痛药剂
A tonic. For pain.
你哪来的
Where did you get it?
兰姆先生给我的
Mr. Lamb gave it to me
-在你出去的时候吗    -不是
-while you were out. -No.
不是
No?
年轻人
Young man...
年轻人   我给过你机会  不是吗
Young man, I offered you an opportunity, did I not?
你还记得
Do you remember?
这个世界   这个广袤的世界 还有那阳光
The world... the vast world, the sunlight.
我曾经怀疑过你会忍不住
I somehow suspected you would find a way
会自轻自贱
to undermine yourself.
虽然我真的  我真的希望你不会这么做
But I did... I hoped against hope that you wouldn't,
但是你还是做了
but you did.
因为你不仅是个傻逼还是个废物
Because not only are you a cretin, you're a failure.
你可真是无可救药 就像其他废物一样
You're a cretinous failure, and like all failures,
你对自己说  我从未有过机会
you say to yourself, "But I never get the chance!
从未得到机遇  但其实并不是这样  不是吗
I never get the opportunity," But it just ain't so, is it?
不
No.
和所有废物一样  你做了什么
And like every failure, what do you do?
你在机会面前退却了
You just piss in the well of possibility.
现在你告诉我是谁给你这药剂的
And now you are going to tell me who gave you the potion.
坚如木条 冰入卵石
Stiff as a stick, cold as a marble.
轻如神灵 自举吾身
Light as a spirit, lift yourself.
轻如羽毛 硬如石板
Light as a feather, stiff as a board.
蜘蛛之王 威力无边
Master spider, stilted or stifled...
编汝之网  回吾之召
Spin us a web and heed our call.
蜘蛛之王 威力无边
Master spider, stilted or stifled,
编汝之网  回吾之召
spin us a web and heed our call.
蜘蛛之王 威力无边
Master spider, stilted or stifled...
谁给你的
Who gave it you?
说 谁给你的
Hmm? Who gave it you?
抬起头来 抬头
Head up. Head up.
-这不是魔药 -不是魔药吗
It's not a potion. - It's not a potion?
这不是魔
It's not a po...
看着我 小子
Look at me, boy.
这 这是药
It's... it's medicine.
我再问一遍
One more time.
我问你的是 谁给你的
I'm going to ask you, who gave it to you?
蜘蛛之王 威力无边
Master spider, stilted or stifled,
吐丝结网 尊崇召唤
spin us a web and heed our call.
蜘蛛之王 威力无边
Master spider, stilted or stifled...
我要做的就是
What we'll do is this...
这只是药剂
It's medicine.
嘘 别出声
Shh, shh.
我要把你的肚皮撕开
I'm going to slit your belly open.
这只是药剂
It's medicine.
把刀伸进去 再拿出来
I'm going to reach in, pull out,
然后用你自己的肠子把你勒死
and I'm going to throttle you with your own intestines.
尊崇召唤
Heed our call.
蜘蛛之王 威力无边
Master spider, stilted or stifled,
吐丝结网 尊崇召唤
spin us a web and heed our call.
蜘蛛之王 威力无比
Master spider, stilted or stifled...
不 不
No. No. No.
现在 立刻告诉我
Now, you tell me right now,
到底是谁给你的
who gave it to you?!
告诉我 以撒
Tell me, Isaac!
告诉我
Tell me!
西布利夫人连一只蚂蚁都不会伤害的
Mrs. Sibley could bring no harm to a living thing.
如果 如果她给了我这个药剂
If... if she provided me the medicine,
就一定是无害的
that's good enough for me.
西布利夫人 是吗
Mrs. Sibley, eh?
很好
Well done.
没你的事了
Off with you now.
滚
Go.
快滚 别让我看到你
Go on! Out of my sight!
通奸者以撒
Isaac the fornicator!
乔治
George.
George!
乔治
嘿
Hey.
你好 父亲
Hello, father.
告诉过你我会出狱的
Told you I'd get out.
是啊 你说过的
Yes, you did.
我说过这事没完
I told you this weren't over.
如果那些婊子还要你的话 我还是要卖了你
You'll be sold still, if the whores will have you.
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
你会走的
You will.
我让你去哪儿你就去哪儿
You will go where I tell you!
我不会走的
I won't.
不会的
I won't. I...
求你别打了
Please!
亨利 霍普金
Henry Hopkins.
这都是些什么
What is this?
斯戴芬
Stephen.
那个男孩的名字
That's his name, the boy.
他告诉你的
He told you?
是啊
Yep.
他两年都没说话了
Two years without speaking,
你陪了他一天 他就告诉你他的名字
and in one day, he tells you his name.
他肯定很喜欢你 上尉
He must have really taken to you, Captain.
不 我不这么认为
No, I wouldn't say that.
我又能说什么呢
And who could blame him?
男孩子需要关注
Boys need attention
需要体力活消耗过剩的体能
and hard work to burn off their energy.
我也很感激
And I'm grateful...
你的帮助
For your hard work.
这是从我回到镇上以来的第一次
It's the first hours passed since I've come back
把女巫的事情抛到脑后
where I haven't thought about witches.
我想也许我们能过上那样的日子
I supposed one could choose that life...
勤恳的工作 和谐的社区 有爱的家庭
honest work, community, a loving family,
没有女巫的打扰
and not a witch in sight.
也许我们能共同创造这样的生活
Maybe there's hope for us yet.
你
You!
去通知市镇委员
Alert the selectmen.
又发现了一个女巫 跟我走
Another witch has been revealed. Follow me.
又或许不是
Or maybe not.
玛丽 西布利
Mary Sibley!
你丈夫醒了
Your husband is awake.
乔治醒了
George is awake?
开口说话了吗
Has he spoken?
他被人下药 没法开口
He is rendered incapable of speech.
可不管怎样 我已经知道折磨他的人了
Nevertheless, the name of his tormentor has been divulged.
什么意思
What does that mean...
被下药 没法开口
"Rendered unable to speak"?
你认出了这剂药吗
Do you recognize this potion?
是的
Yes.
这是用来止痛的
It's a physic for pain.
我让以撒喂西布利先生吃的
I gave it to Isaac to give to Mr. Sibley.
止痛用的
A physic for pain?
告诉我 区区一剂止痛药
Tell me, would a physic for pain
能让西布利先生没法开口
seal Mr. Sibley's mouth shut...
嘴里还长出了金色蜘蛛网吗
With a golden web?
只是止痛剂
A tonic for pain.
只此而已
Nothing more.
父亲 我想我需要提醒你一下
Might I suggest, father,
西布利夫人的药只是止痛剂
that Mrs. Sibley's tonic is just that,
而那张金色蜘蛛网
and the work of the web is due,
更像是真正女巫的杰作
more likely, to the real witch's spider familiar.
对
Yes.
是有这种可能 搜查整个房子
It's a possibility. Search the house.
等等
Wait!
抱歉 先生
I'm sorry, sir.
你是说蜘蛛吗
Did you say a spider?
这是路易斯家的孩子 曾经被女巫折磨控制过
The Lewis child, once tortured and possessed by witches.
可她现在看着气色很好
Yet now she looks remarkably well.
都是因为西布利夫人的照顾
All due to Mrs. Sibley's kindness.
她救了我
She saved my life.
我当时受尽折磨
I was tortured and tormented,
一心求死
at the verge of begging for death,
是玛丽 西布利把我从恶魔手中救出
and Mary Sibley delivered me from evil.
也正因此我在犹豫要不要说
Which is why I hesitate to say...
你要说什么 姑娘
What is it you have to say, girl?
一天早上
The other morning,
西布利夫人出去做船舶生意
when Mrs. Sibley was out on shipping business...
然后呢
Yes?
我经过了提图芭的房间
I did pass Tituba's room,
看到她在做奇怪的事
and she was doing the strangest thing.
告诉我们 默西 告诉我们你看到了什么
Tell us, Mercy. Tell us what you saw.
她拿着一只蜘蛛放在脖子上
She held a spider to her neck.
然后呢
Yes?
她好像在喂它
She seemed to feed it.
你
You.
过来
Come here.
我在此宣布 以女巫之名
I hereby arrest you...
将你逮捕
On the charge of witchcraft.
守卫
Guards.
-在 先生  -是的 先生
Yes, sir. - Aye, sir.
跟我走
Come with us.